8/2/22, 9:45 AM He Zheng

He Zheng, Software Engineer

ranchardzheng@gmail.com | 15650709876 | Beijing, Haidian District, China https://github.com/ZhengHe-MD | https://zhenghe-md.github.io/blog/

SUMMARY

He has earned a bachelor's degree in Economics and a master's degree in Technology of Computer Application in China. Although he works as a back-end engineer most of the time, he also has some base-level understanding and experience on front-end development, machine learning algorithms and big-data analytics. Eager to learn anything interesting, he is capable of conducting research in unfamiliar fields, producing technical reports or shares, and designing solutions to real problems. He leads a software engineering team under the middle platform department for 2 years at PalFish. The team focuses on improving server-side observability and making the development of OA systems easy.

EXPERIENCE

PalFish, Inc, Software Engineer

2019-04-15 — Present

https://www.ipalfishclass.com/

- Distributed tracing: integrate Jaeger, the distributed tracing system, with the pre-existing
 infrastructure to solve the observability problem. Main works include instrumenting on interprocess calls, writing scripts and documentations to help developers migrate legacy
 microservices seamlessly, and supporting tail-based sampling with OpenTelemetry-Collector.
- Source code search engine: introduce Zoekt, a search engine for code, to answer the question,
 "Who is calling my APIs".
- OA building blocks: build and maintain services that provide shared utilities among OA
 systems developed by different teams, in order to speed up the development process. Typical
 ones are organization architecture, authorization, audit logs and business process management.

iQIYI, Inc, Software Engineer

2017-07-12 — 2019-04-01

https://www.iqiyi.com/common/aboutus.html

 Data labeling: design and develop the multimedia data labeling systems, which becomes the main data source for several AI teams to conduct supervised machine learning.

Madadata, Inc, Front-end Engineer

2016-03-15 - 2017-04-17

https://github.com/Madadata

 Front-end development: intern as an front-end engineer, participate in serveral front-end projects, get hands-on experiences on React and NodeJS.

PUBLICATIONS

Simplify the Basic Artificial Bee Colony Algorithm, IEEE International Conference on

Systems Man and Cybernetics Conference Proceedings

https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/7379506

Testing an evolutionary portfolio algorithm on the CEC2016 real-parameter single objective optimization, 2016 IEEE Congress on Evolutionary Computation (CEC) 2016-07-24 https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/7748321

AWARDS

National Scholarship, Ministry of Education

2015-12-01

EDUCATION

Renmin University of China

2014-09-01 — 2017-07-01

Master - Stochastic Optimization and Image Segmentation, GPA: 3.7/4.0

University of International Business and Economics

2010-09-01 — 2014-07-01

Bachelor - Economics, GPA: 3.7/4.0

SKILLS Prog

Programming Language: Go, Javascript, Python, Java

Web Development: HTTP/gRPC/Thrift, HTML/CSS/React

Data systems: MySQL, TiDB, Prometheus, boltdb, Redis, ElasticSearch, MongoDB, Kafka

LANGUAGES

English (conversational), Mandarin (Native)

INTERESTS

Sports [badminton, soccer]

localhost:4000 1/1